The kettle and the idol
It was done.
It's done?
It's done.
Yay!
I would like to introduce the second of the three major elements.
What is this one?
I have the power of continuity, and I think some of you know that,
I think some of you know that,
I do mimicry every day, and now I do comedy every day,
I think the power of continuity is an important element for me,
I have already done about 500 daily monomaniacs, and I have quite a lot of them,
I have been doing this for about two years,
I have been doing this for about two years, and I think it is important that I have been able to continue to do so,
Also, during the period of self-restraint, I woke up at 6 a.m. every morning for a month and did radio exercises,
During the period of self-restraint, I woke up at 6 a.m. every morning, did radio exercises, and cooked and ate breakfast for a month.
I was able to do that for the entire month,
I was able to do that for a month, and my fans were very proud of my ability to keep going,
I thought that my ability to keep going was something I could be proud of.
Did you decide on your own to start doing daily mimicry?
No, I didn't really start doing it on my own,
I had a chance to learn how to mimic at a live performance,
I had a chance to learn mimicry at a live performance, and the staff told me that I could do it every day,
That's how I started,
I think I did the mimicry by myself at first,
I think I did it by myself at first, but the quality of my impersonations gradually improved,
You were even featured in an article, weren't you?
Yes, that's right. Natali was also featured in the article.
I am sorry about that. I am sorry that Natali-san has featured me in such a silly monologue,
I am grateful for that,
At first, I was really doing an impersonation.At first I was really doing a monomaniac.
Real mimicry.
I was doing impersonations of celebrities and so on,
But gradually I started to add my own arrangements,
I started to add my own arrangements, like the tempura impersonation,
And then I started doing real impersonations of movie posters,
Toward the end of the show, I was doing a lot of monomaniacs, I don't know if you would call them monomaniacs.
Did you come up with these ideas on your own, or did you have a brain who suggested them to you?
Basically, I thought up the ideas on my own,
But there are also requests from fans.
Do you edit them yourself?
I edit them myself.
How is that?
I think it's already possible to edit by fans.
I can only edit on my phone,
I can't use a computer at all,
I can't use a computer at all, but I can do it on my phone,
I often get questions about whether the staff does the editing,
I do all of that myself.
But I do it all myself.
That's amazing.
But do you have any tips on how to keep going?
The trick is that I am a very tedious person.
I don't even go to drink water during lessons because it's too much of a hassle to walk,
I am a real pain in the ass,
Why? It's like it's a hassle for me to stop,
If I stopped, people would come to me and ask me if I was going to do something,
I think that would worry everyone,
I think I would worry about what would happen after I quit, and if that is the case, I think it is better to continue,
I don't like to quit in the middle of a project because I don't like to lose,
I don't like the idea of quitting in the middle of a project,I don't like the idea of quitting in the middle of a project,
I'm taking a break from mimicry right now,
I've been doing it for a little over two years, so I've reached a point where I feel like I can do it until the end of my life,
I think my competitive spirit is one of the keys to my success.
That was an unexpected approach. That's interesting.
I am very happy when women say I'm cool, and I think it's a true feeling when men say I'm cool too, because I want to be exposed to that yellow sensibility. Please come to the show, ladies.
This program is sponsored by Yuichi
Tamago Kakkokari
Ringo Imai-san
Fuuji-san
and Toshikazuchan!
Please make Hayashi Rice for dinner tonight!